[Music]
[Applause]
part
two number seven who is interested in
working overtime this
weekend a it won't go over well with
them B I don't mind coming in on
Saturday C Jason's meeting his friends
on the
weekend number eight it appears as
though there's heavy traffic on this
road a the item is heavier than I
thought B we'd better take a detour then
C I rode on the roller coaster
there number nine could you please mail
this letter sometime before noon a she
wrote that she's doing well B about 10
minutes to 12 C
I'll take care of it right
now number 10 how are non-members
supposed to reserve
seats a try calling the box office B
we're in the front row C I'll reserve a
car later
today number 11 why didn't you answer
the phone when I called you
a that's right I called you twice B I
always answer my phone C I was in a
meeting with my
boss number 12 what seems to be the
problem with the new
intern a yes it's rather
problematic B he isn't very
energetic C she applied for that
position
number
13 I may be mistaken but I believe the
seminar will start at 3 a steak and
potatoes for dinner B at least three
more people C yes that seems to be
correct number
14 have you heard who's getting promoted
this
quarter a either Tina or may b a brand
new promotion C several of our
products number 15 when is the new
employee orientation session being held
a for a couple of hours B it's being led
by Mr Morrison C this Thursday morning
number
16 could I borrow some money to pay for
these items
please a who did you borrow it from B
yes I'll pay for everything C sure how
much do you
need number
17 isn't Washington Consulting helping
us with the ad
campaign a the ad will be airing for the
first time tonight B no we couldn't
reach an agreement with them C he's a
new addition to the
workforce number
18 what was the reason that sales
dropped so
dramatically a the quality of the
product B It's a drama on television C
sorry for dropping it
number
19 how is the real estate market in the
suburbs around the city a a house in the
downtown area B three bedrooms at least
C it could be a lot
better number 20 will the package be
delivered by the end of the day a that's
what the career told me b you can go
ahead and sign for it C yes let's have a
pizza
delivered number 21 would you like to
apply for a membership card a he's a
member of this gym B this is an
application form C actually I already
have
one number 2 too Mr Thomas should give
you a call soon shouldn't he a sure go
ahead B call me later see I sure hope
so number
23 where should we put all of these
empty
bottles a I'll take a bottle of soda
please B in the recycling bin over there
C I just put them over
there number
24 to whom was the letter Mr Daniel sent
addressed a I'm not sure how to spell
that b Alice Kenworth I believe C his
address is 22 Wilson
Street number
25 we ought to attend the conference in
New Orleans this month a that's what I
told Mr Barnes B from August 10th to
14th C on new marketing
techniques number
26 can you help me process all of these
order forms this
afternoon a I'd love to but I've got a
meeting B I'm going to order them in a
few minutes C yes I always help her with
her
work number
27 how long does it take to get from
here to the Theater
District a somewhere around 20 minutes B
no more than 3 km away C the show starts
at A4
7 number 28 isn't Miss carendo supposed
to be joining us for
breakfast a bacon and eggs with toast B
no for lunch this
afternoon see we thoroughly enjoyed
it number
29 I hear that danielson's is having a
special promotion this
weekend a I relax that home last
Saturday B she's trying to promote her
new book C
that's right everything's on
sale number 30 would you rather shop
online or visit the shopping mall a
let's do our shopping in person today B
I spend a few hours a day on the
internet c a new mall just opened
downtown last
week number 31
did you answer all of the questions on
the application
form a I got questions two and nine
wrong B I'm pretty sure that I did C
show me the answers you
[Music]
got number seven
who is interested in working overtime
this
weekend a it won't go over well with
them B I don't mind coming in on
Saturday C Jason's meeting his friends
on the
weekend number eight it appears as
though there's heavy traffic on this
road a the item is heavier than I
thought B we'd better take a det or then
C I rode on the roller coaster
there number nine could you please mail
this letter sometime before noon a she
wrote that she's doing well B about 10
minutes to 12 C I'll take care of it
right
now number 10 how are non-members
supposed to reserve
seats a try calling the box office B
we're in the front row C I'll reserve a
car later
today number 11 why didn't you answer
the phone when I called you a that's
right I called you twice B I always
answer my phone C I was in a with my
boss number 12 what seems to be the
problem with the new
intern a yes it's rather
problematic B he isn't very
energetic C she applied for that
position number
13 I may be mistaken but I believe the
seminar will start at 3
a steak and potatoes for dinner B at
least three more people C yes that seems
to be
correct number
14 have you heard who's getting promoted
this
quarter a either Tina or may b a brand
new promotion C several of our products
number
15 when is the new employee orientation
session being held a for a couple of
hours B it's being led by Mr Morrison C
this Thursday
morning number
16 could I borrow some money to pay for
these items
please a who did you borrow it from B
yes I'll pay for everything C sure how
much do you
need number
17 isn't Washington Consulting helping
us with the ad
campaign a the ad will be airing for the
first time
tonight B no we couldn't reach an
agreement with them C he's a new
addition to the workforce
number
18 what was the reason that sales
dropped so
dramatically a the quality of the
product B It's a drama on television C
sorry for dropping
it number
19 how is the real estate market in the
suburbs around the
city a a help in the downtown area B
three bedrooms at least C it could be a
lot
better number 20 will the package be
delivered by the end of the day a that's
what the career told me B you can go
ahead and sign for it C yes let's have a
pizza delivered
number 21 would you like to apply for a
membership card a he's a member of this
gym B this is an application form C
actually I already have
one number
22 Mr Thomas should give you a call soon
shouldn't he a sure go ahead B call me
later
C I sure hope
so number
23 where should we put all of these
empty
bottles a I'll take a bottle of soda
please B in the recycling bin over there
C I just put them over
there number
24 to whom was the letter Mr Daniel sent
addressed a I'm not sure how to spell
that b Alice Kenworth I believe C his
address is 22 Wilson
Street number
25 we ought to attend the conference in
New Orleans this month a that's what I
told Mr Barnes B from August 10th to
14th C
on new marketing
techniques number
26 can you help me process all of these
order forms this
afternoon a I'd love to but I've got a
meeting B I'm going to order them in a
few minutes C yes I always help her with
her
work number
27 how long does does it take to get
from here to the Theater
District a somewhere around 20 minutes B
no more than 3 km away C the show starts
at A4
7 number 28 isn't Miss Carpenter
supposed to be joining us for
breakfast a bacon and eggs with toast B
no for lunch this afternoon C we
thoroughly enjoyed
it number
29 I hear that danielson's is having a
special promotion this
weekend a I relaxed at home last
Saturday B she's trying to promote her
new book C that's right everything's on
sale number 30 would you rather shop
online or visit the shopping mall a
let's do our shopping in person today B
I spend a few hours a day on the
internet c a new mall just opened
downtown last
week number
31 did you answer all of the questions
on the application
form a I got questions two and nine
wrong B I'm pretty sure that I did C
show me the answers you
got for